<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Jamie Tian Real Estate]]></title><description><![CDATA[Jamie Tian]]></description><link>https://www.jamietian.com/blog</link><generator>RSS for Node</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 00:31:14 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.jamietian.com/blog-feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title><![CDATA[Economic update for the week ending March 9, 2019
]]></title><description><![CDATA[February job growth stalls with only 20,000 new jobs added - The Labor Department reported that just 20,000 new jobs were added in...]]></description><link>https://www.jamietian.com/post/economic-update-for-the-week-ending-march-9-2019</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5c836320e1673f001c4d6f5f</guid><category><![CDATA[Economic Update]]></category><category><![CDATA[Mortgage Rates]]></category><category><![CDATA[Stock Market]]></category><category><![CDATA[Luxury Real Estate]]></category><category><![CDATA[International Real Estate]]></category><category><![CDATA[Real Estate]]></category><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2019 06:58:18 GMT</pubDate><dc:creator>Jamie Tian</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>February job growth stalls with only 20,000 new jobs added - The Labor Department </strong>reported that just <strong>20,000 new jobs were added in February. </strong>It marked the fewest jobs added since September 2017. Experts predicted 180,000 new jobs. Considering January’s job growth was so robust, we have still added about 325,000 jobs for the year. </p>

<p><strong>The unemployment rate dropped to a 50 year low of 3.8%</strong>. Average <strong>hourly wages grew 3.4%</strong> from last February, the highest year over year increase in wages since the expansion began 10 years ago. </p>
<p>
<strong>Stocks down for the week - </strong>Fears of slowing global growth weighed heavily on investors as stock markets closed lower every day this week. The Bank of Canada, European Central Bank, and the Chinese government all acknowledged that their economies had slowed and took measures to boost their economies. The <strong>Dow Jones Industrial Average</strong> closed the week at<strong> 25,450.24, down 2.2% </strong>from 26,026.32 last week. It’s up 9.1% year to date. <strong>The S&P 500 </strong>closed the week at <strong>2,743.07, down 2.2% </strong>from 2,803.69 last week. It is up 9.4% year to date. <strong>The NASDAQ </strong>closed the week at <strong>7,408.14, down 2.5% </strong>from 7,595.35 last week. The NASDAQ is up 11.6% year to date. 
</p>
<p><strong>Treasury Bond Yields up sharply this week - </strong>The <strong>10-year treasury bond </strong>closed the week yielding <strong>2.62%, down from 2.76%</strong> last week. <strong>The 30-year treasury bond yield </strong>ended the week at <strong>3.00%, down from 3.13% </strong>last week. We watch treasury bond yields because mortgage rates follow bond yields. </p>

<p><strong>30-year mortgage rates slightly higher in survey, but rates dropped at end of the week - The March 7, 2019 Freddie Mac Primary Mortgage Survey </strong>reported that the <strong>30-year fixed mortgage rate average was 4.41%, up from 4.35%</strong> last week. <strong>The 15-year fixed was 3.83%, up from</strong> 3.77% last week. The 5-year<strong> ARM was 3.87%, almost unchanged </strong>from 3.84% last week. Next week’s rates should be closer to last week’s rates. </p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Revitalization and Development in Downtown Los Angeles!]]></title><description><![CDATA[Just a little over a decade ago, Downtown Los Angeles (DTLA) was merely a sleepy office district, where tens of thousands of office...]]></description><link>https://www.jamietian.com/post/revitalization-and-development-in-downtown-los-angeles</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5c802eb052e469001b602487</guid><category><![CDATA[Real Estate]]></category><category><![CDATA[Economic Update]]></category><category><![CDATA[Homebuyers]]></category><category><![CDATA[First Time Homebuyers]]></category><category><![CDATA[Downtown Los Angeles]]></category><category><![CDATA[Downtown LA]]></category><category><![CDATA[DTLA]]></category><category><![CDATA[DTLA Condos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Downtown LA Condos]]></category><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 20:46:41 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/3733ed857eb7499abd1aef936c96d734.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Jamie Tian</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/3733ed857eb7499abd1aef936c96d734.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure><p>Just a little over a decade ago, Downtown Los Angeles (DTLA) was merely a sleepy office district, where tens of thousands of office workers would go to work during the day and clear out by dusk. Many of the classic Beaux-Arts and Art Deco buildings were abandoned and sat empty. The area didn't even have a grocery store until Ralphs opened approximately 10 years ago.</p>

<p>Today, you see cranes and construction around every corner of the 5.85 square mile area, and the nightlife is bustling with new restaurants and bar openings every month. New buildings are being constructed, existing structures are being renovated, and the public transportation continues to be expanded and improved.</p>

<p>There is a new generation of residents living in DTLA now, and they love the urban lifestyle, the walkability, and the lack of commute to work. According to the business improvement district's year-end market report in 2018, the current construction projects will add more than 7,000 new residential units, and over 35,000 are in the works. Additionally, almost 3 million square feet of office space is under construction and another 3.3 million square feet is in the pipeline.</p>

<p>With the Olympics coming to Los Angeles in 2028, the pace of development and construction over the next 10 years will likely continue to grow. The city's long term vision projects 125,000 residents, 70,000 residential units, and 55,000 jobs in the area by 2040.</p>

<p>Downtown Los Angeles seems to be a great long term investment in 2019 and there is so much opportunity for growth. </p>

<p>Contact me via phone/text at (310) 717-1321 or email at JamieTian@gmail.com if you are interested in finding more about property values in Downtown LA!</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Economic Update For The Week Ending March 2, 2019
]]></title><description><![CDATA[Stocks ended the week slightly higher - Gains in January and February marked the best two month start of a year since 1987 - This week...]]></description><link>https://www.jamietian.com/post/economic-update-for-the-week-ending-march-2-2019</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5c7d843bcd208f001bda6c98</guid><category><![CDATA[Economic Update]]></category><category><![CDATA[Mortgage Rates]]></category><category><![CDATA[Stock Market]]></category><category><![CDATA[International Real Estate]]></category><category><![CDATA[Homeownership]]></category><category><![CDATA[Luxury Real Estate]]></category><category><![CDATA[LA Condos]]></category><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2019 20:04:18 GMT</pubDate><dc:creator>Jamie Tian</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Stocks ended the week slightly higher - Gains in January and February marked the best two month start of a year since 1987 -</strong> This week the March 1 deadline for a deal with China on trade was officially extended as both sides announced that progress has been made. The fourth quarter GDP, the broadest measure of economic output, came in at 2.6%. It was feared in the fourth quarter of 2018 that tariffs, slowing economies overseas, and higher interest rates were slowing the economy. While 2.6% did represent a slowing in the economy, it was slightly higher than what analysts expected. For the full year, GDP rose 2.9%.  For some reason treasury bond Investors pulled back on purchases and yields rose about .10% this week. That will cause mortgage rates to rise about 1/8%-1/4% after almost three months of steadily dropping. </p>

<p><strong>The Dow Jones Industrial Average closed the week at 26,026.32, unchanged</strong> from 26,031.81 last week. It’s up 11.6% year to date. <strong>The S&P 500 </strong>closed the week at <strong>2,803.69, up 0.4% </strong>from 2,792.67 last week. It is up 11.8% year to date. <strong>The NASDAQ </strong>closed the week at <strong>7,595.35, up 0.9% </strong>from 7,527.54 last week. The NASDAQ is up 14.5% year to date. 
</p>
<p><strong>Treasury Bond Yields up sharply</strong> <strong>this week - </strong>The <strong>10-year treasury bond </strong>closed the week yielding <strong>2.76%, up sharply</strong> <strong>from</strong> 2.65% last week. <strong>The 30-year treasury bond yield </strong>ended the week at <strong>3.13%, up </strong>from 3.02% last week. We watch treasury bond yields because mortgage rates follow bond yields. </p>

<p><strong>30-year mortgage rate at lowest level in one year, but rates rose at the end of the week - The February 28, 2019 Freddie Mac Primary Mortgage Survey </strong>reported that the <strong>30-year fixed mortgage rate average was 4.35%, unchanged </strong>from 4.35% last week. <strong>The 15-year fixed was 3.77% almost unchanged from</strong> 3.81% last week. The 5-year<strong> ARM was 3.84%, unchanged </strong>from 3.84% last week. <strong>Rates rose late in the week. Next weeks rates will be higher. </strong></p>

<p><strong>February employment numbers will be released next Friday. They will be included in next weeks report!</strong></p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Economic update for the week ending February 23, 2019
]]></title><description><![CDATA[US stock markets are up more than 18% in nine weeks - Stock markets have made up nearly all the declines suffered in the last three...]]></description><link>https://www.jamietian.com/post/economic-update-for-the-week-ending-february-23-2019</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5c719905e51d0a001c0be34c</guid><category><![CDATA[Real Estate]]></category><category><![CDATA[Economic Update]]></category><category><![CDATA[Stock Market]]></category><category><![CDATA[Mortgage Rates]]></category><category><![CDATA[Homeownership]]></category><category><![CDATA[First Time Homebuyers]]></category><category><![CDATA[Homebuyers]]></category><pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 19:05:12 GMT</pubDate><dc:creator>Jamie Tian</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>US stock markets are up more than 18% in nine weeks -</strong> Stock markets have made up nearly all the declines suffered in the last three months of 2018. Indexes are now approaching their all time highs reached last fall. Experts point to investors' renewed confidence based on three key issues:</p>

<p><strong>1) Progress in the US - China trade negotiations.</strong> </p>
<p>In the third quarter of 2018 it appeared an all out trade war was beginning. Both countries began experiencing slowing in the economy. In fact, China’s economy showed drops in economic output, not the US. Fears that their slowing economy would impact ours spooked investors here. A deal was made to pause any further tariffs until March to give the two countries time to make a deal. While no official deal has been finalized that deadline has been extended, because talks are proceeding positively. It appears that a deal will include provisions for China to encourage more purchasing of US goods with targets to close the tremendous trade imbalance between the countries.</p>

<p><strong>2) Corporate earnings beat expectations. </strong></p>
<p>Analysts had expected corporate earnings to weaken in the fourth quarter because economies in Europe and Asia had slowed. That did not happen.</p>

<p><strong>3) Investors had grown cautious that interest rate hikes by the Federal Reserve would slow the economy.</strong></p>

<p>Investors felt that the Fed had moved to quickly by hiking rates so many times over the last three years. Those fears added to a reason that the stock market began to collapse at the end of last year (December 2018 was the worst December stock market loss since the Great Depression). In reaction to that drop the Fed announced that they would pause further interest rate hikes. Minutes from their latest meeting released this week showed that members voted unanimously to leave rates unchanged, and that they were planning no hikes for 2019 if conditions remain unchanged<strong>. </strong></p>

<p><strong>The Dow Jones Industrial Average closed the week at 26,031.81, up 0.6% </strong>from 25,883-25 last week. It’s up 11.6% year to date. <strong>The S&P 500 </strong>closed the week at <strong>2,792.67, up 0.6%  </strong>from 2,775.50 last week. It is up 11.4% year to date. <strong>The NASDAQ </strong>closed the week at <strong>7,527.54, up 0.7% </strong>from 7,472.71 last week. The NASDAQ is up 13.4% year to date.   </p>

<p><strong>Treasury Bond Yields almost unchanged this week. </strong>The <strong>10-year treasury bond </strong>closed the week yielding <strong>2.65%, down slightly slightly from</strong> 2.66% last week. <strong>The 30-year treasury bond yield </strong>ended the week at <strong>3.02% up slightly</strong> from 3.00% last week. We watch treasury bond yields because mortgage rates follow bond yields. </p>

<p><strong>30-year mortgage rate at lowest level in one year - The February 21, 2019 Freddie Mac Primary Mortgage Survey </strong>reported that the <strong>30-year fixed mortgage rate average was 4.35%, down </strong>from 4.37% last week. <strong>The 15-year fixed was 3.78%, down from</strong> 3.81% last week. The 5-year<strong> ARM was 3.84%, down </strong>from 3.88% last week. </p>

<p><strong>January 2019 California existing home sales report - The California Association of Realtors</strong> released their data for January home sales. The number of sales dropped for the fourth straight month hitting the lowest level since April 2008. <strong>Closed escrows on existing homes dropped to 357,530 units on a seasonally adjusted annualized basis in January. That marked a 12.6% year over  drop</strong> from 409,520 closings last January. This data is for closed escrows so we are talking about homes that went under contract between October and December. This was at the same time that the stock market dropped almost 20%. People were in a panic and that affected home purchases. Now that stocks have made back over 18% of those losses we see buyers returning to the market. Interest rates have also dropped to the lowest level in one year. </p>

<p><strong>We have seen a drastic improvement in the number of homes that have gone into escrow in the last two weeks. It’s like someone flipped a switch and homes are selling briskly again. Unfortunately, those homes won’t close escrow for 30-60 days so we won’t see the impact until March or April in the data. Those should be very positive reports when these sales begin to close.</strong> February’s home sales report will be another disappointing month because that is closings for homes that went under contract in December and January. </p>

<p><strong>The median price paid for a home in California was $538,690, up 2.1% year over year from $527,780 last January.</strong> The median price is the point at which 1/2 the homes sell for more and 1/2 sell for less. While we look at how low the median price is compared to  prices in out market it’s easy to assume that it has nothing to do with us, but over the 30 years that I have been following this data it’s amazing at how neighborhoods at all price levels follow similar percent increases and decreases as the median price percentages. It’s a reliable indicator of what is going on across all price levels. Unfortunately, the median price is compared year over year. Nobody looks at six months ago until now. The median price is 2.1% higher than last January. Prices spiked in April, May and June when inventory hit all time lows. Prices increases were approaching 10% year over year for the first time since 2014. That corrected from July to October and prices actually dropped before stabilizing again. The median price is about 8% below its peak in June, but  higher than last January. Interest rates have also fallen from their peak of 5% to about 4.3% making homes more affordable. </p>

<p><strong>Inventory levels have risen for the 10th consecutive month</strong> after dropping for three straight years to historic lows. <strong>There was a 4.6 month supply of homes for sale in January, up from a 3.6 month supply in January 2018.</strong> There are more choices for buyers. We are seeing many buyers that couldn’t find a home last year and gave up returning to the market. </p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Blair House Condos - Wilshire Corridor in Westwood (90024) - For Sale &#38; For Lease]]></title><description><![CDATA[The Blair House Condominiums, located at 10490 Wilshire Blvd, Los Angeles, CA 90024 is one of the most exclusive and luxurious...]]></description><link>https://www.jamietian.com/post/the-blair-house-condos-wilshire-corridor-in-westwood-90024-for-sale-for-lease</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5c6fa296c18e74001de65546</guid><category><![CDATA[Wilshire Corridor]]></category><category><![CDATA[Westwood]]></category><category><![CDATA[Westwood Condos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Wilshire Corridor Condos]]></category><category><![CDATA[LA Condos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Luxury Condos]]></category><category><![CDATA[LA Condo Buildings]]></category><category><![CDATA[Full Service Condos]]></category><category><![CDATA[High Rise Condos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Los Angeles Condos]]></category><pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 07:25:04 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/7995d1_a8aaab8450b641aca0caaa0046d81d27~mv2_d_5760_3840_s_4_2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Jamie Tian</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/7995d1_a8aaab8450b641aca0caaa0046d81d27~mv2_d_5760_3840_s_4_2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure><p>The Blair House Condominiums, located at 10490 Wilshire Blvd, Los Angeles, CA 90024 is one of the most exclusive and luxurious residential buildings in the Wilshire Corridor of Westwood. The Wilshire Corridor is one of the best places to live in Los Angeles because it is just minutes from UCLA, Santa Monica Beach, the Los Angeles Country Club, Rodeo Drive, Westfield Century City, the Beverly Center Shopping Mall, and more!</p>

<p>Built in 1989, the Blair House is a 29-story, 128-unit building and consists of 2 to 4 bedroom homes ranging from approximately 1600 to 7600 square feet and offers panoramic views from the Pacific Ocean to downtown Los Angeles. The full service building provides amenities such as a pool, fitness center, valet parking, concierge, doorman, and is one of the few buildings on the Wilshire Corridor with its own tennis court</p>

<p>The Korean pop star, Psy purchased a south-facing, unit in the building in 2012. </p>

<p>The Wilshire Corridor is a great place to purchase a property if you are interested in a luxurious full service condo lifestyle in a great, easily accessible location. There are a wide range of options and prices of properties for sale and also for lease in this area.</p>

<p>Please feel free to contact me anytime via phone/text at (310) 717-1321 or email at JamieTian@gmail.com if you are interested in buying, selling, or leasing a unit in the Blair House or anywhere else in the Wilshire Corridor and greater Los Angeles area. I would be happy to email you an updated list of available properties in any building you are interested in!</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Regatta, The Cove, &#38; Azzurra Condos - Marina del Rey (90292) - For Sale &#38; For Lease]]></title><description><![CDATA[Marina del Rey is one of the largest man-made small boat harbors in the United States! The area is known for its contemporary resort...]]></description><link>https://www.jamietian.com/post/regatta-the-cove-azzurra-condos-marina-del-rey-90292-for-sale-for-lease</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5c6f9fdd7c7483001cfe5c4c</guid><category><![CDATA[LA Condos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Luxury Condos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Full Service Condos]]></category><category><![CDATA[High Rise Condos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Los Angeles Condos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Marina del Rey]]></category><category><![CDATA[Silicon Beach]]></category><category><![CDATA[Silicon Beach Condos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Ocean View Condos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Marina del Rey Condos]]></category><pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 07:18:38 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/7995d1_f055b13f5a814733a9498805e30b33d8~mv2_d_2592_1944_s_2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Jamie Tian</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/7995d1_f055b13f5a814733a9498805e30b33d8~mv2_d_2592_1944_s_2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure><p>Marina del Rey is one of the largest man-made small boat harbors in the United States! The area is known for its contemporary resort style luxury condominiums and offers a relaxed pace of life with amazing ocean, mountain, and city views.
</p>
<p>The Regatta, Azzurra, and Cove make up an exclusive condominium community in Marina del Rey. Each offers amazing views through floor-to-ceiling windows, oversized balconies, custom cabinetry, granite countertops, and Grohe and Kohler fixures. Amenities include an Olympic-sized heated pool, a full-sized health spa/cardio theater, landscaped sun decks, a DVD screening room with Dolby sound, secured-access high speed elevators, business/conference room, as well as 24-hour concierge and valet parking.
</p>
<p><strong><u>Regatta</u></strong></p>
<p>The Regatta is located at 13600 Marina Pointe Drive, Marina del Rey, CA 90292. Completed in 1999, this 20-story, 224-unit condo offers 1 to 3 bedroom units ranging from approximately 1,579 to 1,900 square feet. There are currently 3 units for sale ranging from $1,030,000 to $1,999,000 and 1 unit for lease at $5,500/month.</p>

<p><strong><u>The Cove</u></strong></p>
<p>The Cove is the newest of the three condos located at 13650 Marina Pointe Drive, Marina del Rey, CA 90292. Completed in 2006, this 19-story, 138-unit condo offers 1-3 bedroom units ranging from approximately 749 square feet to 3,848 square feet. This building offers the largest 3 bedroom penthouses between the three buildings. There are currently 5 units available for sale ranging from $1,285,000 to $2,995,000 and 3 units for sale ranging from $6,295 to $12,995/month.</p>
<p>
<strong><u>Azzurra</u></strong></p>
<p>Italian for "sky blue", the Azzurra is located at 13700 Marina Pointe Drive, Marina del Rey, CA 90292. Completed in 2003, this 19-story, 450-unit condo offers 1-3 bedroom units ranging from approximately 749 square feet to 3,111 square feet. There are currently 9 units available in the building for sale ranging from $729,000 to $2,549,000 and 7 units available for lease ranging from $3,250 to $9,300/month.</p>

<p>If you are interested in finding out more about any of these condos or if you would like to receive an updated list of available properties in the building, please feel free to call/text me anytime at (310) 717-1321 or email me at JamieTian@gmail.com.</p>
<p>
</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Shoreham Towers - Hollywood Hills (90069) - For Sale &#38; For Lease]]></title><description><![CDATA[The Shoreham Towers is a full service luxury condominium located at the base of the Hollywood Hills, within walking distance to the...]]></description><link>https://www.jamietian.com/post/the-shoreham-towers-hollywood-hills-90069-for-sale-for-lease</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5c6f99e67dee88001c52a768</guid><category><![CDATA[Luxury Condos]]></category><category><![CDATA[LA Condo Buildings]]></category><category><![CDATA[Full Service Condos]]></category><category><![CDATA[High Rise Condos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Los Angeles Condos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Hollywood Condos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sunset Strip]]></category><category><![CDATA[West Hollywood]]></category><category><![CDATA[Hollywood Hills]]></category><category><![CDATA[Hollywood Hills Condos]]></category><pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 06:48:36 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/7995d1_c24b7ec0f3304afca9302d32a745cbd4~mv2.png/v1/fit/w_573,h_435,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Jamie Tian</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/7995d1_c24b7ec0f3304afca9302d32a745cbd4~mv2.png/v1/fit/w_573,h_435,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure><p>The Shoreham Towers is a full service luxury condominium located at the base of the Hollywood Hills, within walking distance to the famous Sunset Strip. The building is conveniently and centrally located at 8787 Shoreham Dr, Los Angeles, CA 90069, within an easy commute to Downtown Los Angeles, Beverly Hills, and Santa Monica.</p>

<p>Located on the corner of Horn Avenue and Shoreham Drive, the 13-floor building has a variety of sizes and types of units including studios, one bedrooms, and two bedrooms.</p>

<p>The Shoreham Towers offers spectacular unobstructed views of downtown Los Angeles as well as the mountains with floor to ceiling windows. The building boasts of amenities such as 24-hour security, a sundeck, pool and spa area, private balconies, and a dog park.</p>

<p>There are currently 5 units available for sale in the Shoreham Towers ranging from $585,000 to $2,495,000 and also 5 units available for lease ranging from $3700 to $4500/month.</p>

<p>Please feel free to contact me anytime via phone/text at (310) 717-1321 or via email at JamieTian@Gmail.com if you are interested in buying, selling, or leasing a unit in the Shoreham Towers or anywhere else in the Greater Los Angeles area. </p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Sierra Towers of the Sunset Strip - West Hollywood (90069) - For Sale &#38; For Lease]]></title><description><![CDATA[The Sierra Towers, designed by architect Jack A. Charney, is located at 9255 Doheny Road, West Hollywood, CA 90069 at the base of the...]]></description><link>https://www.jamietian.com/post/the-sierra-towers-of-the-sunset-strip-west-hollywood-90069-for-sale-for-lease</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5c6f98ca0a2463001c91d698</guid><category><![CDATA[Hollywood Hills Condos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Hollywood Hills]]></category><category><![CDATA[West Hollywood]]></category><category><![CDATA[Luxury Condos]]></category><category><![CDATA[LA Condo Buildings]]></category><category><![CDATA[Full Service Condos]]></category><category><![CDATA[High Rise Condos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Los Angeles Condos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Sunset Strip]]></category><category><![CDATA[Luxury Real Estate]]></category><pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 06:42:18 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/7995d1_ae006e47f4c84cd09e1fe377eca1d147~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_991,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Jamie Tian</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/7995d1_ae006e47f4c84cd09e1fe377eca1d147~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_991,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure><p>The Sierra Towers, designed by architect Jack A. Charney, is located at 9255 Doheny Road, West Hollywood, CA 90069 at the base of the Hollywood Hills just off the famous Sunset Strip. </p>

<p>The Sierra Towers is often considered the most luxurious and exclusive residential condo in all of Los Angeles. The building offers panoramic views of all of Los Angeles from the mountains to downtown LA to the Pacific Ocean, and boasts of amenities and services including 24-hour valet and concierge services, pool, spa, fitness center, ballroom, catering kitchen, and more. The 32-story building was originally built in 1964 and has 146 units. Each floor has around 6 units, but some units have been combined over the years. The units typically have one to three bedrooms and floor to ceiling windows. </p>

<p>Some celebrities who have owned units in the building Elton John, Lindsay Lohan, Matthew Perry, Cher, Courtney Cox, and Brody Jenner.</p>

<p>The building is unique in that it is 15 stories taller than any other building in a two-mile radius, giving it unobstructed views. With current zoning and building restrictions, there will unlikely be another similar tower built in the surrounding area.</p>

<p>There are currently 10 properties for sale in the building ranging from $2,499,000 to $38,000,000. million. There is 1 property currently being offered for lease at $8,750 per month.</p>

<p>The Sierra Towers is a great place to purchase a property if you are interested in a luxurious Hollywood lifestyle. Of course, there are also other more affordable buildings and condos in the West Hollywood/Sunset Strip area. </p>

<p>Please feel free to contact me anytime via phone/text at (310) 717-1321 or via email at JamieTian@gmail.com if you are interested in buying, selling, or leasing a unit at the Sierra Towers or Greater Los Angeles area, or if you would like me to send you an updated list of available units in the building.</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Solair - Mid Wilshire/Koreatown (90010) - For Sale &#38; For Lease ]]></title><description><![CDATA[The Solair is a luxury contemporary high-rise residential building in the Koreatown/Mid-Wilshire area of Los Angeles. It was constructed...]]></description><link>https://www.jamietian.com/post/the-solair-mid-wilshire-koreatown-for-sale-for-lease</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5c6f96a73b84a1001cd92770</guid><category><![CDATA[Los Angeles Condos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Full Service Condos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Koreatown]]></category><category><![CDATA[High Rise Condos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Koreatown Condos]]></category><category><![CDATA[LA Condo Buildings]]></category><category><![CDATA[Luxury Condos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Ktown]]></category><category><![CDATA[Ktown Condos]]></category><category><![CDATA[LA Condos]]></category><pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 06:33:55 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/7995d1_5de9deb8816c4cda84e87e656630a191~mv2.png/v1/fit/w_631,h_357,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Jamie Tian</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/7995d1_5de9deb8816c4cda84e87e656630a191~mv2.png/v1/fit/w_631,h_357,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure><p>The Solair is a luxury contemporary high-rise residential building in the Koreatown/Mid-Wilshire area of Los Angeles. It was constructed in 2008 is located at 3785 Wilshire Blvd, Los Angeles, CA 90010 at the corner of Wilshire Blvd and Western Ave.</p>

<p>The 22-story building contains 186 luxury condominiums over a two-story retail plaza. The Solair is right along the Metro line and its central location makes it a short drive to Beverly Hills, Hollywood, Santa Monica, or Downtown Los Angeles.</p>

<p>Each unit contains large, open floor plans, floor to ceiling windows, and oversized terraces to enhance the spectacular views of Hollywood and downtown LA. Other features include Italian ceramic tiles, hardwood and stone floors, Bosch stainless steel appliances, Caesar Stone countertops, Bontempi Casa Italian cabinets, and oversized soaking tubs. The full service building offers amenities such as a pool, spa, clubhouse, business center, exercise center, concierge, and security.</p>

<p>Each unit ranges in size from 1,331 square feet to 2,900 square feet. </p>

<p>Currently, there are 4 units for sale and 2 units for lease in the Solair.</p>

<p>For Sale:
2 bed, 2 bath - $899,888
2 bed, 2 bath - $919,000
3 bed, 3 bath - $1,495,000
3 bed, 4 bath - $2,750,000
</p>
<p>For Lease:</p>
<p>2 bed, 2 bath - $4000/month</p>
<p>2 bed, 2 bath - $4300/month</p>

<p>Please feel free to contact me anytime via phone/text at (310) 717-1321 or via email at JamieTian@gmail.com if you are interested in purchasing, leasing, or selling a unit in The Solair or anywhere else in the greater Los Angeles area. I would be happy to email you an updated list of available properties in the building!</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Evo South Lofts - Downtown Los Angeles (90015) - For Sale &#38; For Lease]]></title><description><![CDATA[The Evo South is a contemporary style residential condominium built in 2008 in the South Park neighborhood of Los Angeles. The Evo South...]]></description><link>https://www.jamietian.com/post/the-evo-south-lofts-downtown-los-angeles</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5c6f90f79dfdd9001c17bffb</guid><category><![CDATA[Downtown LA Condos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Full Service Condos]]></category><category><![CDATA[DTLA Condos]]></category><category><![CDATA[High Rise Condos]]></category><category><![CDATA[DTLA]]></category><category><![CDATA[Downtown LA]]></category><category><![CDATA[Downtown Los Angeles]]></category><category><![CDATA[Luxury Condos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Downtown LA Lofts]]></category><category><![CDATA[DTLA Lofts]]></category><pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 06:11:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/7995d1_d2cd0d747e98450da1c6c2d7195d8344~mv2_d_5760_3840_s_4_2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Jamie Tian</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/7995d1_d2cd0d747e98450da1c6c2d7195d8344~mv2_d_5760_3840_s_4_2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure><p>The Evo South is a contemporary style residential condominium built in 2008 in the South Park neighborhood of Los Angeles. The Evo South is located at 1155 S Grand Ave, Los Angeles, CA 90015, and stands near its sister buildings, the Elleven South Lofts and the Luma. 

The 24 story building boasts of unobstructed views of the Staples Center, Ritz Carlton, LA Live, Hollywood Hills, and Pacific Ocean! The South Park neighborhood is great because it is walking distance to LA Live, the Staples Center, and the Financial and Garment districts.

There are 311 lofts and condos and 5 two-story town-homes with exclusive private gardens. The units range from 730 to 3500 square feet and the residents enjoy amenities such as the gym, media roo6m, pool, spa, 24-hour concierge, and rooftop lounge.

The Evo South is the first building high-rise residential building in downtown Los Angeles to be designated LEED silver by the US Green Building Council. The building was designed using energy saving technologies, renewable and recyclable materials, and environmentally responsible construction techniques.

There are currently 7 units available for sale ranging from $634,000 to $2,100,000 and 9 units available for lease ranging from $2600 to $6700/month.</p>

<p>Please feel free to call/text me at (310) 717-1321 or email JamieTian@gmail.com for an updated list of available units or to schedule a viewing!</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[1100 Wilshire Blvd - Downtown Los Angeles (90017) - For Sale &#38; For Lease]]></title><description><![CDATA[1100 Wilshire was originally an office building located in Downtown Los Angeles that was converted to a full service luxury residential...]]></description><link>https://www.jamietian.com/post/1100-wilshire-blvd-downtown-los-angeles</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5c6f8ec69dfdd9001c17bc9c</guid><category><![CDATA[Downtown Los Angeles]]></category><category><![CDATA[Downtown LA]]></category><category><![CDATA[DTLA]]></category><category><![CDATA[High Rise Condos]]></category><category><![CDATA[DTLA Condos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Downtown LA Condos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Full Service Condos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Downtown LA Lofts]]></category><category><![CDATA[DTLA Lofts]]></category><category><![CDATA[Los Angeles Condos]]></category><pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 06:03:51 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/7995d1_917c6c75a9624b558cc1f28a7b275fc5~mv2_d_3830_2554_s_4_2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Jamie Tian</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/7995d1_917c6c75a9624b558cc1f28a7b275fc5~mv2_d_3830_2554_s_4_2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure><p>1100 Wilshire was originally an office building located in Downtown Los Angeles that was converted to a full service luxury residential condominium. The condos are on floors 17-37 and there are 12 levels of parking. The address of the building is 1100 Wilshire Blvd, Los Angeles, CA 90017.</p>

<p>Each unit has granite countertops, stainless steel appliances, and floor to ceiling corner views from Century City to the Hollywood Hills. On the 17th floor, there is an open-air deck with heated pool, cabanas, fire pit, and BBQ facilities. The building also offers 24-hour security, exercise room, a business center, and a movie theather.</p>

<p>I am representing unit 1812 for sale at $499,000. It is 1 bedrooms, 1 bathrooms, 720 sq ft with views over the pool deck and panoramic views of the city. The property also features in unit laundry and 2 parking spaces. I will be holding an open house there this Sunday 2/24 from 2:00 to 4:00pm. Please feel free to come by for a tour of the unit and the building!</p>

<p>There are also 7 other units for sale currently on the market ranging from $499,000 to $1,950,000 and 3 units for lease ranging from $2850 to $4200/month.</p>

<p>Please feel free to call/text me anytime at (310) 717-1321 or email me at JamieTian@gmail.com for an updated list of available units or to schedule a viewing!</p>

]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Residences at W Hollywood (900298) - For Sale &#38; For Lease]]></title><description><![CDATA[The Residences at the W in Hollywood represents the epitome of luxury condominiums and is located on the world famous intersection of...]]></description><link>https://www.jamietian.com/post/the-residences-at-w-hollywood-for-sale-for-lease-90028</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5c6f883cc81052001cc55fed</guid><category><![CDATA[Los Angeles Condos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Hollywood]]></category><category><![CDATA[Hollywood Condos]]></category><category><![CDATA[High Rise Condos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Full Service Condos]]></category><category><![CDATA[LA Condo Buildings]]></category><category><![CDATA[Luxury Condos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Hollywood]]></category><category><![CDATA[Hollywood Condos]]></category><category><![CDATA[LA Condos]]></category><pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 05:34:33 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/7995d1_b860313cf34b4131b30990c0bb3d1d2b~mv2.png/v1/fit/w_751,h_498,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Jamie Tian</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/7995d1_b860313cf34b4131b30990c0bb3d1d2b~mv2.png/v1/fit/w_751,h_498,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure><p>The Residences at the W in Hollywood represents the epitome of luxury condominiums and is located on the world famous intersection of Hollywood Blvd and Vine at 6250 Hollywood Blvd, Los Angeles, CA 90028. With spectacular views of the city and the Hollywood Hills including the iconic Hollywood sign and Capitol Records Building, the W Residences offers full service condo living in the heart of Hollywood.</p>

<p> The 143-unit condo offers its residents an impressive rooftop park, pool, outdoor kitchen and dining area, fitness area, dog park, as well as 24-hour valet parking and concierge services.</p>

<p>The W Hollywood is a LEED-compliant property and combines sustainability with contemporary design and technology to offer the ultimate luxury lifestyle. The property includes the W Hotel, the W Residences, the Bliss Spa, and some of L.A.'s most popular nightclubs and restaurants.</p>

<p>Currently there are 13 units in the building for sale ranging from $795,000 to $6,995,000. There are currently 5 units in the building available for lease ranging from $4795 to $7250/month.</p>

<p>Please feel free to contact me via phone/text at (310) 717-1321 or email me at JamieTian@gmail.com for an updated list of available units or with any real estate related needs or questions!</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Ritz Carlton Residences at LA Live - Downtown Los Angeles (90015) - For Sale &#38; For Lease]]></title><description><![CDATA[The Ritz-Carlton Residences at L.A. Live is located in downtown Los Angeles in a world famous sports and entertainment district at 900 W....]]></description><link>https://www.jamietian.com/post/the-ritz-carlton-residences-at-la-live-downtown-los-angeles</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5c6f360d2dfdb0001ca61f67</guid><category><![CDATA[Los Angeles Condos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Downtown Los Angeles]]></category><category><![CDATA[Downtown LA]]></category><category><![CDATA[DTLA]]></category><category><![CDATA[High Rise Condos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Downtown LA Condos]]></category><category><![CDATA[DTLA Condos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Full Service Condos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Luxury Condos]]></category><category><![CDATA[LA Condos]]></category><pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 01:13:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/7995d1_cf01cec056924f4fa26302ea5f51b965~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_480,h_600,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Jamie Tian</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/7995d1_cf01cec056924f4fa26302ea5f51b965~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_480,h_600,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure><p>The Ritz-Carlton Residences at L.A. Live is located in downtown Los Angeles in a world famous sports and entertainment district at 900 W. Olympic Blvd, Los Angeles, CA 90015. Within walking distance are popular bars, clubs, restaurants, movie theaters, museums, and sports events at the Staples Center. It is also within a few miles of USC.</p>

<p>There are 224 units spanning from the 27th floor to the 52nd floor. Each unit features floor to ceiling glass windows with amazing views of all of Los Angeles. Residents enjoy amenities such as the rooftop swimming pool and spa, valet parking, 24 hour concierge/doorman, complimentary buffet breakfast daily, a Wolfgang Puck restaurant, and the spa and fitness centers. Residents also have access to the amenities at the Ritz Carlton hotel and the JW Marriott Hotel. The interior of the units are contemporary in design and include designer kitchen appliances and fixtures.</p>

<p>The building was designed by Gensler, an international architecture and design firm, and is LEED-certified (silver) by the U.S. Green Building Council. It is one of the most sustainable buildings in downtown L.A!</p>

<p>There are currently 15 units available for sale, ranging from $1,095,000 to $7,750,000. Each unit has 1 to 3 bedrooms and 1.5 to 3.5 bathrooms. There are currently 6 units in the building available for lease, ranging from $5100 to $13,000 per month. I also have some off market pocket listings that you may be interested, contact me for more details!</p>

<p>Please feel free to contact me via phone/text at (310) 717-1321 or JamieTian@gmail.com if you are interested in buying, selling, or leasing a unit in the Ritz Carlton Residences or anywhere in the greater Los Angeles area!</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Pros and Cons of a Homeowner's Association (HOA)]]></title><description><![CDATA[A homeowners association, commonly referred to as a HOA, is a group organized to create and enforce rules for a neighborhood or a...]]></description><link>https://www.jamietian.com/post/pros-and-cons-of-a-homeowner-s-association</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5c6f3406159e5f001c11a894</guid><category><![CDATA[Real Estate]]></category><category><![CDATA[Selling Your Home]]></category><category><![CDATA[Homebuyers]]></category><category><![CDATA[Buying A Home]]></category><category><![CDATA[First Time Homebuyers]]></category><category><![CDATA[Chinese Buyers]]></category><category><![CDATA[HOA]]></category><category><![CDATA[Homeowner's Association]]></category><category><![CDATA[Homeownership]]></category><pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 01:13:13 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/7995d1_4f3e4ea025344c5c91436c5e9cb63160~mv2_d_4608_3072_s_4_2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Jamie Tian</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/7995d1_4f3e4ea025344c5c91436c5e9cb63160~mv2_d_4608_3072_s_4_2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure><p>A homeowners association, commonly referred to as a HOA, is a group organized to create and enforce rules for a neighborhood or a condominium building/complex. Its goal is generally to maintain an overall conformity to protect the property values of the community. The HOA must abide by the CC&Rs (Covenants, Conditions, & Restrictions) that were originally set up for governing the community. Monthly or annual dues are generally collected and used to maintain and upkeep common areas and amenities. Each HOA has its own rules and regulations and provides different services. It is important to find out about all the rules and policies of the HOA before purchasing a property.</p>
<p>There are many pros and cons to living in a community with a HOA:</p>

<p><u><strong>Pros</strong></u><strong>:</strong></p>
<p><strong>Maintenance</strong> - HOA's maintain and pay for common areas and amenities provided by the community or building. This often includes swimming pools, parks, tennis courts, gym, etc.</p>
<p><strong>Services:</strong> - HOA's often also provide services to its building or neighborhood. This can include neighborhood/building security, street sweeping, valet parking, etc.</p>
<p><strong>Property Value</strong> - HOA's regulate certain factors to keep conformity and help keep the neighborhood/building attractive. These rules regarding paint colors, renovation restrictions, and rules about signs around the neighborhood help to maintain property values.</p>
<p><strong>Mediation</strong> - HOA's can help to resolve disputes between neighbors quickly so that no hard feelings are left over.</p>

<p><u><strong>Cons</strong></u><strong>:</strong></p>
<p><strong>Intrusive</strong> - Too many rules can be annoying and you may want to paint your house a certain color that's not allowed.Sometimes the rules may seem unreasonable.</p>
<p><strong>Expensive</strong> - HOA monthly fees can be expensive and are another bill to be added to the list of expenses. HOA fees are usually higher in full service condominiums with valet parking, 24-hour security, concierge, swimming pools, and exercise facilities.</p>
<p><strong>Fines</strong> - You may face fines if you break the rules!</p>

<p>Please feel free to contact me if you have any questions about HOAs, or would like help buying, selling, or leasing a property! You can reach me anytime via phone/text at (310) 717-1321 or via email at JamieTian@gmail.com.</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Caimeiju - International Marketing For Chinese Buyers with Rodeo Realty  ]]></title><description><![CDATA[Rodeo Realty is an affiliate with Caimeiju, a site dedicated to advertising and marketing luxury California real estate to Chinese...]]></description><link>https://www.jamietian.com/post/caimeiju-international-marketing-for-chinese-buyers-with-rodeo-realty</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5c6f23aa26832c001c71f705</guid><category><![CDATA[Real Estate]]></category><category><![CDATA[Selling Your Home]]></category><category><![CDATA[Buying A Home]]></category><category><![CDATA[First Time Homebuyers]]></category><category><![CDATA[Chinese Buyers]]></category><category><![CDATA[International Real Estate]]></category><pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 01:13:08 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/7995d1_194ddf9667b64e34ba9cd67f6b32348f~mv2.png/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Jamie Tian</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/7995d1_194ddf9667b64e34ba9cd67f6b32348f~mv2.png/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure><p>Rodeo Realty is an affiliate with Caimeiju, a site dedicated to advertising and marketing luxury California real estate to Chinese markets and investors. Chinese buyers are playing an increasingly large role in purchasing U.S. luxury real estate.
</p>
<p>All of my listings over $1M are translated into Chinese by professional linguists, making our properties and company information searchable in China. Zillow and many other major real estate websites are blocked using a firewall by the Chinese government, so your listings are not searchable on Chinese search engines!</p>

<p>Our listings are shared through Chinese social media, real estate, and video sharing websites, and can be found on top Chinese local search engines like Baidu, Google China, Bing.CN, and Yahoo Taiwan with top Chinese keywords. This enables Rodeo Realty to be fully represented in Asian markets.
</p>
<p>I am fluent in Mandarin Chinese and would be happy to represent you in the sale or purchase of a property. Feel free to contact me anytime via call/text at (310) 717-1321 or email at JamieTian@gmail.com. </p>

<p>I would love to talk to you about more about our company or provide a free professional estimate of your home value. If you are searching for your dream home to purchase, I would be happy to send you a list of available properties that fit your search criteria and help you set up appointments to view any properties you are interested in.</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[How to Interview a Realtor When Selling a Home
]]></title><description><![CDATA[One of the most important decisions you have to make when selling your home is choosing the right realtor. If you choose the right...]]></description><link>https://www.jamietian.com/post/how-to-interview-a-realtor-when-selling-a-home</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5c6f209be51d0a001c06684f</guid><category><![CDATA[Selling Your Home]]></category><category><![CDATA[Real Estate]]></category><pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 01:13:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/7995d1_69c2616779714795a0937a913451ad16~mv2_d_4000_4000_s_4_2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Jamie Tian</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/7995d1_69c2616779714795a0937a913451ad16~mv2_d_4000_4000_s_4_2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure><p>One of the most important decisions you have to make when selling your home is choosing the right realtor. If you choose the right realtor to represent your property, your home will sell quickly and for the highest price.</p>

<p><strong>1) Are you a full time real estate agent? </strong></p>
<p>You don’t want someone who obtained their real estate license for fun or as a hobby, or has another full or part time job that they need to attend to. The agent listing your home needs to be able to show your property at any time of the day so you don’t lose out on potential buyers.</p>

<p><strong>2) How do you plan on marketing my home? </strong></p>
<p>This is extremely important because you don’t want an agent that will just take some cell phone photos, stick a sign in your yard and list the property on the MLS. A good Realtor will use professional photography and video to showcase your home, as well as a combination of both print and internet marketing strategies to attract potential buyers. Some examples include newspaper ads, mailers, email blasts, social media posts, targeted social media ads, common online websites such as Zillow, Trulia, Realtor.com and Homes.com, as well as international real estate websites such as Caimeiju and Juwai which cater to buyers in China, and LuxuryRealEstate and PrestigeMLS, which cater to buyers in Europe and the Middle East.</p>

<p><strong>3) Will you be holding public open houses as well as broker caravan tours? </strong></p>
<p>Weekend open houses give buyers the flexibility to view the property when they are not at work, and some buyers are hesitant to call and schedule a viewing of a property if they are not 100% sold on the property after reading the description and looking at the photos, but would still come by the open house just to check it out. The more buyers you get through the door, the faster you will find a buyer. A crowded open house can also play on buyers' fears and motivate them to act quickly. In Los Angeles, we do weekly Tuesday Broker’s Caravan Tours, which gives agents a chance to preview new listings in their area and stay on top of the inventory, as well as pre-screen properties for their clients so that they only show their clients the homes that are the best fit for them.</p>

<p><strong>4) How will you communicate with me and when is the best time to contact you. </strong></p>
<p>A good agent should be willing to communicate with you in whatever method you prefer, whether it be email, phone, text, WeChat, WhatsApp, or in person. You should be able to reach your agent 24/7 and they should alway be quick to respond.</p>

<p><strong>5) Do you have any references or reviews? </strong></p>
<p>The best agents will have a website with positive reviews from past clientele. You can learn a lot about the way an agent conducts their business, their responsiveness, and their professionalism by reading their reviews.</p>

<p>These are the 5 most important questions to ask a real estate agent when interviewing them to list your home. If you choose the wrong agent, you will waste time and your listing will become stale, which will affect the ultimate sales price of your home. Even if you eventually hire another realtor, many buyers will not be interested in a home that has been re-listed several times with different realtors. </p>

<p>If you have any questions about how to pick the best Realtor to represent your home, you can contact me via phone/text at (310) 717-1321 or email at <a href="mailto:JamieTian@gmail.com" target="_top" rel="noopener"><u>JamieTian@gmail.com</u></a>.</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Should I Buy A Home In 2019?
]]></title><description><![CDATA[People ask me every day if its a good time to buy a home in 2019. I’ll tell you 5 reasons why it’s a great time to buy a home! 1) The...]]></description><link>https://www.jamietian.com/post/should-i-buy-a-home-in-2019</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5c6f1fe62dfdb0001ca5e78f</guid><category><![CDATA[Real Estate]]></category><category><![CDATA[Homebuyers]]></category><category><![CDATA[Buying A Home]]></category><category><![CDATA[First Time Homebuyers]]></category><pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 01:12:56 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/7995d1_ae0728ef84d94df4b6ed884e62721409~mv2_d_5760_3840_s_4_2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Jamie Tian</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/7995d1_ae0728ef84d94df4b6ed884e62721409~mv2_d_5760_3840_s_4_2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure><p>People ask me every day if its a good time to buy a home in 2019. I’ll tell you 5 reasons why it’s a great time to buy a home!</p>

<p>1) The interest rates are the lowest they have been in 9 months! The average rate for a 30 year fixed rate mortgage was 4.6% at the end of January 2019. Although this is slightly higher than a few years ago, it is still historically low, with rates reaching up to 18% in the 1980s! A higher interest rate increases your monthly payment, which lowers the overall purchase price you can afford.</p>

<p>2) 2019 is less of a Seller’s Market than it has been in the past few years because the inventory is not as limited as before and the buyer pool is smaller. I am no longer seeing as many multiple offer situations and crazy bidding wars, which means there are more opportunities to find good deals.</p>

<p>3) If you are still renting, you are literally losing that money every time you pay rent. When you own a home and take out a mortgage, you are contributing each month to your principal and growing your home equity, which you can borrow against in the future if you need it. Also your interest rates are tax deductible. Who doesn’t want to pay less income taxes? A fixed rate mortgage doesn’t change so your monthly payments will continue to stay the same, while your landlord can increase your rent each year. Not to mention, you have the pride of ownership and the freedom to renovate your home however you like.</p>

<p>4) Real estate investments have traditionally been a terrific inflation hedge to protect against a loss in the purchasing power of the dollar over time. Historically, the real estate market is much less volatile and unpredictable than other types of investments such as the stock market.</p>

<p>5) Real estate is a tangible investment, you can physically walk into and inspect the property you want to purchase. If you buy rental properties early in life, you can use the rental income to pay off the mortgage and eventually have passive recurring income.</p>

<p>These are my top 5 reasons on why it is a great time to buy a home in 2019. If you have any questions about any of these topics or are interested in purchasing a home in Los Angeles, you can reach me via phone/text at (310) 717-1321 or via email at <a href="mailto:JamieTian@gmail.com" target="_top" rel="noopener"><u>JamieTian@gmail.com</u></a>.</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Economic update for the week ending - February 16, 2019]]></title><description><![CDATA[Stock markets had another strong week - Stock markets surged again this week. The S&#38;P which was down nearly 20% from its all time high in...]]></description><link>https://www.jamietian.com/post/economic-update-for-the-week-ending-february-16-2019</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5c6f1de83b84a1001cd807df</guid><category><![CDATA[Economic Update]]></category><category><![CDATA[Real Estate]]></category><category><![CDATA[Mortgage Rates]]></category><category><![CDATA[Stock Market]]></category><pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 01:12:51 GMT</pubDate><dc:creator>Jamie Tian</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Stock markets had another strong week -</strong> Stock markets surged again this week. The S&P which was down nearly 20% from its all time high in December is now just 6% below its all time high. It’s up 10.7% in just the first 6 weeks of the year.<strong> </strong></p>

<p><strong>This week’s highlights:</strong> Investors were optimistic that a trade deal would be made soon ending the tariffs that have been put in place by both the US and China. President Trump said the March 1 deadline would be extended, leading investors to believe progress has been made. In fact, he said “it will be the best deal ever!” Another government shutdown was averted. Oil prices rose after Saudi Arabia agreed to cut output to reduce surplus oil levels which helped energy stocks. This all seemed to offset disappointing final December retail sales figures. </p>

<p><strong>The Dow Jones Industrial Average closed the week at 25,883.25, up 3.1% </strong>from 25,106.33 last week. It is up 11.0% year to date. <strong>The S&P 500 </strong>closed the week at <strong>2,775.50, up 2.5% </strong>from 2,707.88 last week. It is up 10.7% year to date. <strong>The NASDAQ </strong>closed the week at <strong>7,472.41, up 2.4% </strong>from 7,298.20 last week. It is up 12.6% year to date. 
</p>
<p><strong>Treasury Bond Yields almost unchanged this week - </strong>The <strong>10-year treasury bond </strong>closed the week yielding <strong>2.66%, up slightly from</strong> 2.63% last week. <strong>The 30-year treasury bond yield </strong>ended the week at <strong>3.00%, up slightly</strong> from 2.97%  last week. We watch treasury bond yields because mortgage rates follow bond yields. </p>

<p><strong>Mortgage rates continue to drop - Rates are at the lowest levels since February 2018 - The February 14, 2019 Freddie Mac Primary Mortgage Survey </strong>reported that the <strong>30-year fixed mortgage rate average was 4.37%, down </strong>from 4.41% last week. <strong>The 15-year fixed was 3.81%, down from</strong> 3.84% last week. The 5-year<strong> ARM was 3.88%, down </strong>from 3.91% last week. </p>
<p><strong>Homes were more affordable in the fourth quarter of 2018 - The California Association</strong> of Realtors announced that their home <strong>affordability index rose in the fourth quarter of 2018 to 28%, up from 27% in the third quarter, </strong>but still less affordable than one year ago when the affordability index stood at 29%. Lower prices and higher wages offset higher interest rates in the fourth quarter and affordability rose.</p>

<p><strong>In the fourth quarter the median priced detached home was $564,270. The California Association of Realtors reported that a minimum annual income of $122,340 was needed to qualify for a monthly payment of $3,060, including principal, interest and property taxes on a 30-year fixed loan of 4.95%. </strong></p>

<p><strong>Affordability on a $460,000 median-priced condo or town-home was 37% in the fourth quarter of 2018. An annual income of $99,730 was needed to qualify for a monthly payment of $2,490.</strong> On a regional basis the affordability index in <strong>Los Angeles Country was 24%,</strong> up from 22% in the second quarter, but down from 25% in Q4 2017<strong>.</strong> In <strong>Orange County affordability was just 20%</strong> in both Quarter 3 and Q4 2018, down from 21% in Q4 2017.  <strong>Ventura County Q4 affordability was 29%,</strong> up from 28% in Q3, and up from 26% in  Q4 2017. </p>
<p>Interest rates peaked in the fourth quarter of 2018. In October the 30-year fixed rate hit 5%! </p>

<p><strong>Rates are now down over one half percent.</strong> They are at the lowest levels in one year. That should boost affordability when the first quarter of 2019 figure is announced in May. Prices were also lower in the fourth quarter of 2018 than at their  peak in the second quarter. In fact, it appears that the median price peak of $602,760 in June was an outlier, as buyer’s panicked just to get a home with inventory levels at record lows. Inventory levels rose in the fourth quarter and prices stabilized back down to first quarter 2018 levels. The median price was $564,760 and $557,600 In November and December respectively.  I’m looking forward to seeing the first quarter 2019 affordability level. I won’t be surprised if affordability is back up to almost 30% as rates are lower, incomes which have been increasing about 3.2% annually are higher, and prices I expect will be about the same as in the fourth quarter.</p>
]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[5 Best Home Renovations to Boost Sale Value!
]]></title><description><![CDATA[Sellers looking to put their home on the market in the near future always ask me what renovations they can do to boost their sale value....]]></description><link>https://www.jamietian.com/post/5-best-home-renovations-to-boost-sale-value</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5c6f19a5fbc02d001c70a644</guid><category><![CDATA[Home Renovation]]></category><category><![CDATA[Real Estate]]></category><category><![CDATA[Selling Your Home]]></category><category><![CDATA[Home Remodel]]></category><pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 01:12:43 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/7995d1_b7359b6e72d84678884ee326c9906afa~mv2_d_2666_4000_s_4_2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Jamie Tian</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/7995d1_b7359b6e72d84678884ee326c9906afa~mv2_d_2666_4000_s_4_2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure><p>Sellers looking to put their home on the market in the near future always ask me what renovations they can do to boost their sale value. According to HGTV, here are the top home updates that actually pay off!</p>

<p><strong>1) Minor Bathroom Remodel: Average Return at Resale - 102%</strong></p>
<p>Replace tub, tile, flooring, toilet, sink, vanity, and fixtures. Repaint. Replace old shower doors to remove them alltogether to create the illusion of a larger space.</p>

<p><strong>2) Landscaping: Average Return at Resale - 100%</strong></p>
<p>The front of your home is the first impression on a buyer! Add colorful flower and plants, a fountain, or trim back overgrown plants.</p>

<p><strong>3) Minor Kitchen Remodel: Average Return at Resale - 98.5%</strong></p>
<p>Without redesigning the floor plan, you can resurface cabinets, replace appliances and fixtures, repaint, and change flooring.</p>

<p><strong>4) Exterior Improvements: Average Return at Resale - 95.5%</strong></p>
<p>Repaint the exterior wall and doors, remove old awnings, fix cracked concrete, etc.</p>

<p><strong>5) Attic Bedroom Conversion: Average Return at Resale - 93.5%</strong></p>
<p>Adding a bonus room to your property is always desirable!</p>

<p>Of course, every property and neighborhood is different! If you are trying to decide what kind of updates would most benefit the future sale of your phone, feel free to give me a call/text at (310) 717-1321 or email me at JamieTian@gmail.com for a free professional consultation from a real estate agent!</p>
]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Elleven South Lofts - Downtown Los Angeles (90015) - For Sale &#38; For Lease]]></title><description><![CDATA[The Elleven South Lofts, built in 2006, is the first green residential building constructed in Downtown Los Angeles. It is located in the...]]></description><link>https://www.jamietian.com/post/elleven-south-lofts-downtown-los-angeles</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5c6f3f89f94d7d001c538188</guid><category><![CDATA[Los Angeles Condos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Downtown Los Angeles]]></category><category><![CDATA[Downtown LA]]></category><category><![CDATA[DTLA]]></category><category><![CDATA[High Rise Condos]]></category><category><![CDATA[Full Service Condos]]></category><category><![CDATA[LA Condo Buildings]]></category><category><![CDATA[Luxury Condos]]></category><category><![CDATA[DTLA Lofts]]></category><category><![CDATA[Downtown LA Lofts]]></category><pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 01:12:29 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/7995d1_ffe71dfa7bd24c2dbd81bef2a28acd8b~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_853,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Jamie Tian</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/7995d1_ffe71dfa7bd24c2dbd81bef2a28acd8b~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_853,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure><p>The Elleven South Lofts, built in 2006, is the first green residential building constructed in Downtown Los Angeles. It is located in the South Park neighborhood of downtown on 11th Street and Grand Avenue at 1111 S Grand Ave, Los Angeles, CA 90015.</p>

<p>There are a wide range of units, from studios to penthouse suites. Each unit has bamboo floors, stainless steel appliances, parking, a laundry room, and spectacular views of Downtown LA.</p>

<p>The building has 13 stories and each unit is styled as a "soft loft" with a bedroom/closet area. This means that it is not a traditional loft in the sense that it does not have concrete floors and exposed pipes/duct work. It is more like a condo, but still offers wide and open living spaces with huge windows like a loft.</p>

<p>This building is an entirely new construction and is LEED-certified by the U.S. Green Building Council. </p>

<p>There are currently 5 units for sale in the Elleven South Lofts, starting from $583,500. Each unit has 1-2 bedrooms and 1-3 bathrooms. </p>

<p>Please feel free to contact me via phone/text at (310) 717-1321 or email at JamieTian@gmail.com if you are interested in purchasing, selling, or leasing a property in the Elleven South Lofts, or another property in the greater Los Angeles area. I would be happy to provide you with an update to date list of available properties</p>

]]></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>